<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>online presence on Connecting Thoughts</title>
    <link>https://connectthoughts.com/tags/online-presence/</link>
    <description>Recent content in online presence on Connecting Thoughts</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 21 Oct 2020 23:53:00 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://connectthoughts.com/tags/online-presence/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>How to plan for cloud security in any organization?</title>
      <link>https://connectthoughts.com/blog/cloudwhattodo/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Oct 2020 23:53:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://connectthoughts.com/blog/cloudwhattodo/</guid>
      <description>How to plan for cloud security in any organization? Due to various services and flexibility offered by cloud services, businesses were able to expand rapidly and increase revenue by providing innovative solution to customers. But there are some challenges such as disaster recovery, migrating data to another cloud, and security, which need to be addressed for better cloud compliance in business organizations. There are many security threats in the cloud, such as misconfiguration of cloud services, compliance violation, contractural breaches, and insecure application user API, which can affect the businesses.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Do you need online presence?</title>
      <link>https://connectthoughts.com/blog/online/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Sep 2020 23:53:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://connectthoughts.com/blog/online/</guid>
      <description>Online presence is key, especially now, to showcase your skills and express your thoughts and ideas inS form of blogs or articles. Having your own personal website gives you credibility when someone is searching for your name. In this post, I’m going to discuss the benefits of writing on your own website. Writing is one of the easiest ways to get started, as you need only time with no expensive tools.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>